(Sheldon:)You naughty girl.
(Sheldon:)You went to the Wizarding World
theme park without me.
(Sheldon:)I did.
(Amy:)Am I in trouble?
(Sheldon:)Yes, you're in trouble--
(Sheldon:)you went to Wizarding World
without me!
(Amy:)Wait, what just happened?
(Midwife:)You know
(Sheldon:)I've been wanting to go.
(Amy:)Sheldon, do you
really want to argue with me
(Amy:)on my birthday?
(Sheldon:)Oh, you're right.
(Bernadette:)I'm sorry.
(Amy:)Ooh. Happy birthday to me.
(Raj(off):)Hello...
(Amy:)Is this about the baby?
(Raj:)No. People just keep
kicking me out everywhere I go.
(Amy:)Good. Then you're used to this.
Hey, Bernadette's water broke!
Come on! Everyone
to the hospital!
You have got to be kidding me!